

#### CONTACT

ন্টি 27 Allée Daniel Lavallée 76000, Rouen

+33 7 66 29 08 12

bessa460@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/younesbessa



github.com/YounesBessa

younesbessa.com

#### LANGUAGES

Native language

Fluent (C1 level)

Conversational (B2 Level)

#### SKILLS

•••• HTML

••• CSS

**JavaScript** 

React

Wordpress

# **YOUNES BESSA** 23 YEARS OLD

## JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT ME

I'm a 23-year-old Junior full stack Web developer from France. I study web development at Need for School in Rouen. I'm an apprentice at Expat's Facilities and I'm also part of an association called onRuntime Studio.

I like to play video games, travel and meet new people.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Web Developer (apprenticeship)

Expat's Facilities, Rouen | October 2021 - Present

#### Web Developer (two month internship)

Rouen Informatique, Rouen | April 2021 - June 2021

I designed internal digital tools related to the CRM of the company at the request of the internship supervisor and in compliance with the deadlines.

I analysed the needs and developed all the technical functionalities of these tools. I solved the problems and fixed the bugs detected by the internship supervisor.

Languages: HTML,CSS,PHP,SQL,JS Libraries: libcurl(PHP), jQuery

APIs: Google Maps API (JavaScript), Axonaut API

Framework: Bootstrap CMS: WordPress

#### EDUCATION

### Bachelor's Degree in Web Development

Need for School, Rouen | October 2020 - Present

# Programming languages and tools:

- HTML,CSS
- PHP, Symfony
- MySQL, phpMyAdmin
- JavaScript, React
- JQuery
- Wordpress

## Bachelor's Degree in French Law

(First and second year)

University of Rouen, Pasteur Campus | 2018 - February 2020

# Bachelor's Degree in Economic and Social Administration (First year)

University of Rouen, Pasteur Campus | 2017 - 2018

# French baccalaureate (Economics branch)

French International School, Riyadh | 2017

Cambridge English Advanced Certificate, C1 level

French International High School, Jakarta | 2014